Guide to the Sterling Lord Papers MSS.058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Print Materials, 1950s-2010s; 108 Linear Feet in 108 record cartons.
  - Subseries VI.B: 2017 Accretion
    - The Great American Bomb Machine, 1971 (Box 437, Folder 192)
    - Poe's Heart and the Mountain Climber, 2004 (Box 437, Folder 193)
    - The Brain Has A Mind of It's Own, 1991 (Box 437, Folder 194)
    - Brainscapes, 1995 (Box 437, Folder 195)
    - The Mind, 1988 (Box 437, Folder 196)
    - The Modular Brain, 1988 (Box 437, Folder 197)
    - The Naked Brain, 2006 (Box 437, Folder 198)
    - The New Brain, 2006 (Box 437, Folder 199)
    - The Playful Brain, 2010 (Box 437, Folder 200)
    - Singled Out, 1981 (Box 437, Folder 194)
    - Act of Creation, 2003 (Box 437, Folder 195)
    - The Black Sea, 2001 (Box 437, Folder 196)
    - Blue Movie, 1970 (Box 437, Folder 197)
    - The Arrogance of Power, 2000 (Box 437, Folder 198)
    - Cospiracy, 1980 (Box 438, Folder 199)
    - Sinatra: The Life, 2005 (Box 438, Folder 200)
    - Next Time Is For Life, 1953 (Box 438, Folder 201)
    - Like I Was Sayin..., 1984 (Box 438, Folder 202)
    - Company Man, 1995 (Box 438, Folder 203)
    - Who Runs This Place?, 2004 (Box 438, Folder 204)
    - Charlotte and Lionel, 2003 (Box 438, Folder 202)
    - Upstairs at the White House, 1973 (Box 438, Folder 207)
    - An Illustrated History of the Olympics, 1975 (Box 438, Folder 205)
    - Singled Out, 1981 (Box 438, Folder 206)
    - Act of Creation, 2003 (Box 438, Folder 207)
    - The Black Sea, 2001 (Box 438, Folder 208)
    - The Search for Justice, 1996 (Box 438, Folder 208A)
    - Blue Movie, 1970 (Box 438, Folder 209)
    - The Arrogance of Power, 2000 (Box 438, Folder 210)
    - Conspiracy, 1980 (Box 439, Folder 211)
    - Sinatra: The Life, 2005 (Box 439, Folder 212)
    - Lion Mountain, 1998 (Box 439, Folder 213)
    - On Any Given Sunday, 1984 (Box 439, Folder 214)
    - Ten Circles Upon the Pond, 2003 (Box 439, Folder 215)
    - Next Time is for Life, 1953 (Box 439, Folder 216)
    - Charlotte and Lionel, 2003 (Box 439, Folder 217)
    - 11 Days in December, 2006 (Box 439, Folder 218)
    - Four Rossettis, 1977 (Box 439, Folder 219)
    - London Yankees, 1979 (Box 439, Folder 220)
    - Upstairs at the White House, 1973 (Box 439, Folder 221)
    - Upstairs at the White House, 1973 (Box 440, Folder 222)
    - The Children's Game, 1983 (Box 440, Folder 223)
    - The Espionage Establishment, 1967 (Box 440, Folder 224)
    - The Invisible Government, 1964 (Box 440, Folder 225)
    - Nightmover, 1995 (Box 440, Folder 226)
    - The Politics of Lying, 1973 (Box 440, Folder 227)
    - The Samarkand Dimension, 1987 (Box 440, Folder 228)
    - Spy, 2002 (Box 440, Folder 229)
    - The Spy Who Got Away, 1988 (Box 440, Folder 230)
    - The U-2 Affair, 1960 (Box 440, Folder 231)
    - I.M. Pei, 2001 (Box 441, Folder 232)
    - The End of the Line, 1990 (Box 441, Folder 233)
    - Walking to Vermont, 2004 (Box 441, Folder 234)
    - Big Cotton, 2005 (Box 441, Folder 235)
    - Three Sisters in Black, 1968 (Box 441, Folder 236)
    - Select Editions: Selected and Edited by Reader's Digest, 2008 (Box 441, Folder 237)
- Oversize Series I: Subject Files
  This series contains the oversize material removed from Series I, Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher files.
  - Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher Files
    - Berenstains - Galleys, 1990-1994 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Nesbit correspondence - Photos of Tom Wolfe, 1965 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Newfeld, Jack - The Village Voice - April, May, 1965 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Newfeld, Jack - The Village Voice - June, August, September, October, 1965 (Box 300, Folder 4)